<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:layout_gravity="center"
    android:paddingBottom="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingTop="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin">






    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:id="@+id/SV1"
        android:scrollbars="none">
        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:orientation="vertical">









    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="fill_parent"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:orientation="vertical">
        <com.analytics.bjj.MyTextView
            android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:gravity="center_vertical"
            android:text="About"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:textSize="25sp"/>
    <com.analytics.bjj.MyTextView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:text="BJJ Analytics helps you improve your jiu jitsu game by tracking your tournament match statistics, drills, techniques, and time trained. Analyze your strengths and your weaknesses, retain knowledge more effectively when learning new techniques, and stay motivated with this app. It's easy to use. You can log all your training yourself. There is no limit to what you can achieve in BJJ. Let BJJ Analytics help you achieve your goals."/>
        </LinearLayout>

            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="20dp"></LinearLayout>


            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="fill_parent"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:orientation="vertical">
                <com.analytics.bjj.MyTextView
                    android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:gravity="center_vertical"
                    android:text="Privacy Policy"
                    android:textStyle="bold"
                    android:textSize="25sp"/>
                <com.analytics.bjj.MyTextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="match_parent"
                    android:text="BJJ Analytics ( &quot;us, &quot;  &quot;we, &quot; or  &quot;Company &quot;) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company app (the  &quot;App &quot;). We created this app Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the app, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the app, and not to any other apps that you may be able to access from the app, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.\n\nWhat information do we collect?\nWe collect information from you when you fill out a form.When registering on our app, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. We also collect your training and tournament statistics to aggregate online in order to generate a population database of BJJ practitioners. The population statistics may be available online and is stored on our secure servers. Your individual statistics information will not be personally identifiable. By using this app, you are agreeing to the information collected by this app.\n\nWhat do we use your information for?\nAny of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:\n– To improve our app(we continually strive to improve our app offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)\n– To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)\n– To send periodic emails\nThe email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.\n\nHow do we protect your information?\nWe implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. The app has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.\n\nDo we disclose any information to outside parties?\nWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information without your consent. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our app, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our app policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.\n\nCalifornia Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance\nBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.\n\nChildrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance\nWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our app, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.\n\nGoogle Adsense Privacy Policy Terms\nThird party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this app, BJJ Analytics.\n\nLog Files\nWe use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the app, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used only within BJJ Analytics on a need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable information related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your explicit permission.\n\nYour Consent\nBy using our app, you consent to our privacy policy.\n\nChanges to our Privacy Policy\nIf we decide to change our privacy policy (which is subject to change at any time without notice), we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.\nMarch 11, 2016"/>
            </LinearLayout>


















            </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

</LinearLayout>
